trading-point.com 2017-12-17

# Privacy Policy

**We are committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors and users of this website. Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us. We will only use your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy.**

Our Privacy Policy Statement will be reviewed from time to time to take into account of new laws and technology, changes to our operations and practices and to ensure it remains appropriate to the changing environment. By using this website, you consent to us using your personal information as set out below.

### What personal information do we collect?

If you decide to apply to open an account with us, there is certain information that we will require from you in order to do so. This information includes but is not limited to personal details such as name, address, date of birth, contact details, employment details, assets and liabilities and other necessary financial information. From time to time we may also request further information to help us improve our service to you. We obtain most of the information directly from our customers through application or other forms, and from maintaining records of information provided in the course of on going customer service. We may also collect information about your use of the website, such as pages visited, frequency and duration and visit and trading activities.

### How do we use this information?

We will use information collected from you to provide the information and services requested by you and to improve the quality of our service. Unless you are informed otherwise, the personal information we hold is used for:

  * Establishing and managing your account;
  * Reviewing your ongoing needs;
  * Enhancing customer service and products;
  * Giving you ongoing information or opportunities that we believe may be relevant to you.

### Disclosure of Information

Depending on the product or service concerned and particular restrictions on sensitive information, this means that personal information may be disclosed to: Service providers and specialist advisers to us who have been contracted to provide us with administrative, financial, insurance, research or other services. Introducing brokers with whom we have a mutual relationship (any of whom may be within or outside the European Economic Area) Credit providers, courts, tribunals and regulatory authorities as agreed or authorised by law.

### Credit reporting or reference agencies

Anyone authorized by an individual, as specified by that individual or the contract. If you do not want us to use your personal information please let us know in writing. If you decide to do so, we may not be able to continue to provide information, services and/or products requested by you and we will have no liability to you in respect of the same.

### Updating your information

You may inform Trading Point of Financial Instruments Ltd at any time that your personal details have changed or that you wish Trading Point to delete personal information we hold about you by emailing us at sales@trading-point.com.

Trading Point of Financial Instruments Ltd will change or delete your personal information in accordance with your instructions, except to the extent that we are required to hold your personal information for regulatory or legal purposes, to provide you with the services you have requested or to maintain adequate business records.

### Use of Cookies

If you open an account with us, you will need to use our trading software which enables us to use cookies in relation to your access to this website. Cookies are small files of information, which often include a unique identification number or value, which are stored on your computer’s hard drive as a result of you using this trading software and accessing this website. The purpose of this information is to provide you with a more relevant and effective experience on this website, including presenting web pages according to your needs or preferences. Cookies are frequently used on many websites on the internet and you can choose if and how a cookie will be accepted by changing your preferences and options in your browser. You may not be able to access some parts of this site if you choose to disable the cookie acceptance in your browser, particularly the secure parts of the website. We therefore recommend you enable cookie acceptance to benefit from all the services on the website.

### What are your rights

You have (subject to certain exceptions) the right to obtain any personal information which Trading Point of Financial Instruments Ltd holds about you and inform Trading Point of financial Instruments Ltd of any perceived inaccuracy. To make a request, please write to us, verifying your identity and specifying what information you require. We may charge a fee to cover the cost of verifying the application and locating, retrieving, reviewing and copying any material requested. We will acknowledge your request and respond to it within 40 days of receipt of your application and any applicable fee.

### Amendments to policy

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. If any changes are made an updated version will be posted on this page.

### How to contact us

If you have any questions regarding this policy, wish to access or change your information or have a complaint, please call us on 00357 25029900 or write or e-mail us with your concerns at:

Trading Point of Financial Instruments Ltd  
Richard and Verengaria Street  
Araouzos Castle Court, 3rd floor  
Limassol 3042  
Cyprus
